69pornclips.com 2009-04-22

# DigiDotz - Web Hosting & Web Design

**Legal - Privacy Policy**

\------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------ 

In order to ensure strict privacy of all our customers and site users, we have implemented a Privacy Policy. All handling of identifiable and non-identifiable customer and user information is done according to the provisions in this Policy. 

**Ordering  
** We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and billing information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

**Cookies  
** Our site uses cookies to store your login details and settings for our members area. No personal information is stored in these cookies. 

**Log Files  
** We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing  
** We do not share our customers information with any other parties. 

**Links  
** This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Supplementation of Information  
** In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. For example, if you place an order using your credit card, we may need to submit your billing information to a 3rd party for billing or verification. 

**Site and Service Updates  
** We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via e-mail or phone. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information  
** If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our us at billing@digidotz.com 

**Notification of Changes  
** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
